[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "What happens when you come that day?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happens", "when", "you", "come", "that", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "When I came here in -- in Wild Card, we just came here for just a vacation and looking for a boxing gym for workout.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "came", "here", "in", "--", "in", "Wild", "Card", ",", "we", "just", "came", "here", "for", "just", "a", "vacation", "and", "looking", "for", "a", "boxing", "gym", "for", "workout", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Can you believe what's happened to you in your career?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "believe", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "you", "in", "your", "career", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "I never expected what I have done in boxing and, you know, it's -- it's amazing and unbelievable.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "expected", "what", "I", "have", "done", "in", "boxing", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "amazing", "and", "unbelievable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "It's -- there's a pressure, you know, because all Filipinos, millions of Filipinos, they're hoping for victory in the fight.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "there", "'s", "a", "pressure", ",", "you", "know", ",", "because", "all", "Filipinos", ",", "millions", "of", "Filipinos", ",", "they", "'re", "hoping", "for", "victory", "in", "the", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "How do you feel when people say you're the best fighter there's ever been?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "when", "people", "say", "you", "'re", "the", "best", "fighter", "there", "'s", "ever", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "How I feel -- of course, I feel happy and people believing my talent, my capability in boxing.", "answer_tokens": ["How", "I", "feel", "--", "of", "course", ",", "I", "feel", "happy", "and", "people", "believing", "my", "talent", ",", "my", "capability", "in", "boxing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "How do you manage to try and kill people with your hands but not hate?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "manage", "to", "try", "and", "kill", "people", "with", "your", "hands", "but", "not", "hate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I think this is -- this is part of the -- of the -- my career.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "this", "is", "--", "this", "is", "part", "of", "the", "--", "of", "the", "--", "my", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "What did you hope to achieve when you were doing those fights?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "hope", "to", "achieve", "when", "you", "were", "doing", "those", "fights", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Did you nearly give up then?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "nearly", "give", "up", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "The --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Did you think about giving up then?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "about", "giving", "up", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "When you get in the ring for a fight like you are tomorrow, as you walk in, how do you really feel?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "get", "in", "the", "ring", "for", "a", "fight", "like", "you", "are", "tomorrow", ",", "as", "you", "walk", "in", ",", "how", "do", "you", "really", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "I'm excited and, you know, I've been training eight weeks for this fight.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "excited", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "training", "eight", "weeks", "for", "this", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well, I mean, you know, it's my experience, before a fight, with short hair, I feel like I'm weak.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "my", "experience", ",", "before", "a", "fight", ",", "with", "short", "hair", ",", "I", "feel", "like", "I", "'m", "weak", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "How realistic is this for you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "realistic", "is", "this", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Being a public servant, this is a serious job, not like a boxer, you're entertaining people.", "answer_tokens": ["Being", "a", "public", "servant", ",", "this", "is", "a", "serious", "job", ",", "not", "like", "a", "boxer", ",", "you", "'re", "entertaining", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Philippines"]}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Would you like to be in a position of power to change that, to make it a more honest politics?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "be", "in", "a", "position", "of", "power", "to", "change", "that", ",", "to", "make", "it", "a", "more", "honest", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "That's what I am trying to do, to change the -- you know, the politics in the Philippines.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "I", "am", "trying", "to", "do", ",", "to", "change", "the", "--", "you", "know", ",", "the", "politics", "in", "the", "Philippines", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["millions of dollars"]}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Does it motivate you, money?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "motivate", "you", ",", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Making money -- I'm happy, because, of course, every fight I make millions of dollars.", "answer_tokens": ["Making", "money", "--", "I", "'m", "happy", ",", "because", ",", "of", "course", ",", "every", "fight", "I", "make", "millions", "of", "dollars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "What do you honestly think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "honestly", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "I never, you know -- right now, I'm not thinking about that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", ",", "you", "know", "--", "right", "now", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "thinking", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Would you like to?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Like what I said, I'm more -- you know, I always fight whatever my promoter is giving to me, the opponent.", "answer_tokens": ["Like", "what", "I", "said", ",", "I", "'m", "more", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "always", "fight", "whatever", "my", "promoter", "is", "giving", "to", "me", ",", "the", "opponent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Do you think you'd beat him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "'d", "beat", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "It's hard to say.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "What brought you two together -- fate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "brought", "you", "two", "together", "--", "fate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "CD", "RB", ":", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "I believe so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Can you tell by a fighter's eyes?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "tell", "by", "a", "fighter", "'s", "eyes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Yes, you can.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "What makes Manny special to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "makes", "Manny", "special", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "He's like a son to me.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "like", "a", "son", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Manny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "CD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 209, "question": "And how many Filipinos come and see him?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "many", "Filipinos", "come", "and", "see", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Yes, I get at least about 30 a day that come to the door in --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "get", "at", "least", "about", "30", "a", "day", "that", "come", "to", "the", "door", "in", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Every day in Los Angeles?", "question_tokens": ["Every", "day", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "I mean, is it as crazy as it sounds when he goes back?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "it", "as", "crazy", "as", "it", "sounds", "when", "he", "goes", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "TO", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Apart from God and -- and your worship of God, what are the other things that you think are important in life?", "question_tokens": ["Apart", "from", "God", "and", "--", "and", "your", "worship", "of", "God", ",", "what", "are", "the", "other", "things", "that", "you", "think", "are", "important", "in", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", ":", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Important in life is you know how to -- to love people and to be friendly to everybody.", "answer_tokens": ["Important", "in", "life", "is", "you", "know", "how", "to", "--", "to", "love", "people", "and", "to", "be", "friendly", "to", "everybody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "That's got to hurt you, right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "got", "to", "hurt", "you", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "It's hurt me, but, you know, people don't believe him.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hurt", "me", ",", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "people", "do", "n't", "believe", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 242, "question": "And you really want to beat him, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "really", "want", "to", "beat", "him", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "-- the focus --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "the", "focus", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "I mean more than -- more than most fights?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "more", "than", "--", "more", "than", "most", "fights", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", ":", "JJR", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mayweather"]}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Would he beat Floyd Mayweather?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "he", "beat", "Floyd", "Mayweather", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Yes, we have the right stuff to beat Mayweather.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "have", "the", "right", "stuff", "to", "beat", "Mayweather", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Floyd Mayweather"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "And is -- and is the trump card with Manny that you've -- you've developed now, almost equal power with both hands?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "--", "and", "is", "the", "trump", "card", "with", "Manny", "that", "you", "'ve", "--", "you", "'ve", "developed", "now", ",", "almost", "equal", "power", "with", "both", "hands", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", ":", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Manny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ":", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Why do men want to do this to each other?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "men", "want", "to", "do", "this", "to", "each", "other", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "It's -- it's not only for myself, but, you know, I keep fighting because I want to know I'm happy to give -- giving honor to my country.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "not", "only", "for", "myself", ",", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "keep", "fighting", "because", "I", "want", "to", "know", "I", "'m", "happy", "to", "give", "--", "giving", "honor", "to", "my", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "What do you say to a guy like Manny, who has won everything?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "a", "guy", "like", "Manny", ",", "who", "has", "won", "everything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "You know, we warm up a little bit and go through the routines and when you make this move, you know, what move he is going to make.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "warm", "up", "a", "little", "bit", "and", "go", "through", "the", "routines", "and", "when", "you", "make", "this", "move", ",", "you", "know", ",", "what", "move", "he", "is", "going", "to", "make", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Manny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Do you pray before a fight?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "pray", "before", "a", "fight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Always.", "answer_tokens": ["Always", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Well, you are a singer, right?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "are", "a", "singer", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "After -- after the fight.", "answer_tokens": ["After", "--", "after", "the", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "So you pray before and you sing after?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "pray", "before", "and", "you", "sing", "after", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "After.", "answer_tokens": ["After", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Bob, what makes this guy television promotional gold dust?", "question_tokens": ["Bob", ",", "what", "makes", "this", "guy", "television", "promotional", "gold", "dust", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Because he fights the way people want to see fighters fight, and because his genuine goodness shines through.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "he", "fights", "the", "way", "people", "want", "to", "see", "fighters", "fight", ",", "and", "because", "his", "genuine", "goodness", "shines", "through", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Is that true -- is that true, Manny?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "--", "is", "that", "true", ",", "Manny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Sometimes.", "answer_tokens": ["Sometimes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Manny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "-- why -- why do you do that?", "question_tokens": ["--", "why", "--", "why", "do", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Because I -- I feel it in my heart.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "--", "I", "feel", "it", "in", "my", "heart", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "You feel sorry for them?", "question_tokens": ["You", "feel", "sorry", "for", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Yes, all of them.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "all", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Even when you're pummeling them?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "when", "you", "'re", "pummeling", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Yes, I'm just doing my job.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "just", "doing", "my", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 333, "question": "What's it -- what's it like being hit hard by somebody very, very good?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "it", "--", "what", "'s", "it", "like", "being", "hit", "hard", "by", "somebody", "very", ",", "very", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "It's --", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "I mean, I -- I can imagine, but you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "--", "I", "can", "imagine", ",", "but", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Because if you don't hit hard, your opponent hits you hard.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "hit", "hard", ",", "your", "opponent", "hits", "you", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Do you feel it in the actual moment?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "it", "in", "the", "actual", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "ACQUIAO: You can feel it, but if you -- like if you get hit a good one, you can feel it.", "answer_tokens": ["ACQUIAO", ":", "You", "can", "feel", "it", ",", "but", "if", "you", "--", "like", "if", "you", "get", "hit", "a", "good", "one", ",", "you", "can", "feel", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Does he ever miss and whack you one?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "ever", "miss", "and", "whack", "you", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Manny is very accurate.", "answer_tokens": ["Manny", "is", "very", "accurate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tyson"]}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Of all the boxers, what's been the worst punch you ever had to take?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "the", "boxers", ",", "what", "'s", "been", "the", "worst", "punch", "you", "ever", "had", "to", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "The worst punch I guess was Tyson.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "worst", "punch", "I", "guess", "was", "Tyson", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Where does Manny rank, genuinely, do you think, in the 46 years you've been in the fight game?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "Manny", "rank", ",", "genuinely", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "in", "the", "46", "years", "you", "'ve", "been", "in", "the", "fight", "game", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Well, there was a period of time where Ali was absolutely super, when he became champion and before the draft.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "was", "a", "period", "of", "time", "where", "Ali", "was", "absolutely", "super", ",", "when", "he", "became", "champion", "and", "before", "the", "draft", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Manny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mayweather", "Manny Pacquiao"], "LOCATION": ["U.S.", "Mideast"]}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "How much money could you make from promoting the Pacquiao/Mayweather fight if it ever happened?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "money", "could", "you", "make", "from", "promoting", "the", "Pacquiao/Mayweather", "fight", "if", "it", "ever", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "If I could make that fight happen, then the government, U.S. government might send me over to bring about peace in the Mideast, because I've got a guy in Mayweather who won't fight Manny Pacquiao because no matter what the money is, he knows he will get knocked out.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "make", "that", "fight", "happen", ",", "then", "the", "government", ",", "U.S.", "government", "might", "send", "me", "over", "to", "bring", "about", "peace", "in", "the", "Mideast", ",", "because", "I", "'ve", "got", "a", "guy", "in", "Mayweather", "who", "wo", "n't", "fight", "Manny", "Pacquiao", "because", "no", "matter", "what", "the", "money", "is", ",", "he", "knows", "he", "will", "get", "knocked", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Do you agree with that, Freddie?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "that", ",", "Freddie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Do you respect him or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "respect", "him", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Everybody?", "question_tokens": ["Everybody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Everybody I respect.", "answer_tokens": ["Everybody", "I", "respect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Why do you say that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "You know, America is -- for me, it's the best country.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "America", "is", "--", "for", "me", ",", "it", "'s", "the", "best", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Why do you think that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "The freedom, all the people, you know, and also the Constitution of America.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "freedom", ",", "all", "the", "people", ",", "you", "know", ",", "and", "also", "the", "Constitution", "of", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ":", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Do you worry that you may fight just too long and suffer irreparable damage?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "worry", "that", "you", "may", "fight", "just", "too", "long", "and", "suffer", "irreparable", "damage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "ACQUIAO: Well, I'm -- I'm looking for -- I -- I'm thinking for that -- not to get hurt.", "answer_tokens": ["ACQUIAO", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "'m", "--", "I", "'m", "looking", "for", "--", "I", "--", "I", "'m", "thinking", "for", "that", "--", "not", "to", "get", "hurt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Manny"]}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Are you going to be helping him promote his campaign?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "be", "helping", "him", "promote", "his", "campaign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Well, Manny had me over.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Manny", "had", "me", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2022"]}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "So this could be for both of you the last big hurrah?", "question_tokens": ["So", "this", "could", "be", "for", "both", "of", "you", "the", "last", "big", "hurrah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Well, I'll be -- it keeps me going because in 2022, I'll be 91 years of age, I'll come in on my cane.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ll", "be", "--", "it", "keeps", "me", "going", "because", "in", "2022", ",", "I", "'ll", "be", "91", "years", "of", "age", ",", "I", "'ll", "come", "in", "on", "my", "cane", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Have you worked out your cabinet position yet?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "worked", "out", "your", "cabinet", "position", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Not yet.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 524, "question": "When he goes in the ring and he does the mitts, it goes away, right, Freddie?", "question_tokens": ["When", "he", "goes", "in", "the", "ring", "and", "he", "does", "the", "mitts", ",", "it", "goes", "away", ",", "right", ",", "Freddie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "The tremors go away and the shaking and it's just like --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "tremors", "go", "away", "and", "the", "shaking", "and", "it", "'s", "just", "like", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Why do you think that is?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "that", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I'm not sure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Was that your record?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "your", "record", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I had like a 41-13 record at the end.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "like", "a", "41-13", "record", "at", "the", "end", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Did you think the condition you have now is down to boxing or not?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "the", "condition", "you", "have", "now", "is", "down", "to", "boxing", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "I'm a trauma study.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "trauma", "study", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Do you assume the same about Muhammed Ali?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "assume", "the", "same", "about", "Muhammed", "Ali", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "How do you feel having been his friend for so long?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "having", "been", "his", "friend", "for", "so", "long", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "RUM: And his promoter.", "answer_tokens": ["RUM", ":", "And", "his", "promoter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "How many do you have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "These tattoos, it's is a meteor.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "tattoos", ",", "it", "'s", "is", "a", "meteor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "And that one?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "This is old, when I was young.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "old", ",", "when", "I", "was", "young", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Does it mean anything or no?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "mean", "anything", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "It is a rose with a snake.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "a", "rose", "with", "a", "snake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "It is a green snake.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "a", "green", "snake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Does it have a meaning?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "have", "a", "meaning", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "It means you want to hit people, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "means", "you", "want", "to", "hit", "people", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "There is a rose bud and a snake.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "a", "rose", "bud", "and", "a", "snake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "What are your children's full names?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "children", "'s", "full", "names", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Jimuel, his name is Emanuel Junior.", "answer_tokens": ["Jimuel", ",", "his", "name", "is", "Emanuel", "Junior", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "You named your daughter after my queen?", "question_tokens": ["You", "named", "your", "daughter", "after", "my", "queen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Have you met the queen?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "the", "queen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Do you like the royal family?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "the", "royal", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Why do you like them?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "like", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "I like them, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "them", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "But what else do you think about?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "else", "do", "you", "think", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "My dream is to help people.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "dream", "is", "to", "help", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "Was that -- that was -- was it bigger than Tyson's?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "--", "that", "was", "--", "was", "it", "bigger", "than", "Tyson", "'s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ":", "IN", "VBD", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "A little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tyson"]}}]